itp.nyu.edu 2018-06-29

# Digital Privacy Statement

## Digital Web and Mobile Privacy Statement  

New York University (NYU) is committed to respecting your privacy. This privacy statement governs the collection and use of information collected through official NYU websites and other NYU digital properties.  

### Information Gathering and Use of Information

#### Personally Identifiable Information  

NYU will not collect personally identifiable information about you when you visit our websites or digital properties unless you voluntarily provide us with that information.  NYU may request personally identifiable information from you if you wish, for example, to access a password-protected website, join a mailing list, or engage in a payment transaction.  NYU may use that information for such purposes as fulfilling your requests for our information or services, communication information that may be of interest to you, and conducting research surveys.  NYU will not share your information with third parties except as set forth below under "Sharing Your Information."

Back to Top ^

#### Non-Personally Identifiable Information

When you visit NYU websites and other NYU digital properties, we may automatically collect and store information sent by your web browser, such as IP addresses (i.e., the Internet address of your computer) in server logs. We also collect standard information about your computer (such as your web browser and operating system) and about your usage of our websites and digital properties (such as pages visited, length of visit, and search queries).  This information, which does not identify your personally, is aggregated and used to help diagnose problems and suggest points for improving parts of our website and digital properties. For example, we utilize statistical software to identify which parts of our website are most heavily used and which portion of our audience comes from within the NYU network.

Back to Top ^

#### Cookies  

Like many other websites, portions of NYU's websites and digital properties may use cookies.  Cookies are text files that may be transferred to your computer or mobile device through your web browsing software. These cookies are used to remember your preferences or to track statistics on usage of various portions of NYU websites and digital properties. Our use of cookies does not involve the collection of personally identifiable information.

You can choose not to accept cookies by selection settings on your web browser that block or restrict the use of cookies. You can also delete cookies that have been placed on your computer or device.

For more information about the use of cookies by third parties, see below under "Behavioral Advertising."

Back to Top ^

### Sharing Your Information

In cases when NYU has personally identifiable information (PII) about you, we will not sell, rent, or share that PII and will treat it in compliance with our [Personally Identifiable Information Policy](http://www.nyu.edu/its/policies/pii.html) and with other related institutional policies and federal and state laws and regulations.

Back to Top ^

### Behavioral Advertising  

NYU may contract with third party vendors to show our advertisements on non-NYU websites and digital properties. NYU and third party vendors with whom we contract may use cookies and web beacons to serve our ads based on your prior visit(s) to NYU websites and digital properties and to assess the effectiveness of our ads. This is also called Targeted Advertising or Interest-Based Advertising.  

These techniques use only non-personally identifiable information, and you may opt out of behavioral advertising by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt out page at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

Back to Top ^

### Security  

NYU has implemented reasonable physical, technical, and administrative procedures to safeguard and secure all information we collect online against loss, misuse, or alteration of the information under our control. This includes the use of encryption when collecting or transferring sensitive data such as credit card information. Please note that while we work hard to protect the security of your information, NYU cannot provide an absolute guarantee as to the security of any information you transmit through our websites or digital properties, and that you do so at your own risk.

Back to Top ^

### Third Party Sites  

NYU websites and digital properties may link to external sites that are not controlled by NYU. Your use of such websites will be subject to the privacy statements of those websites, which we encourage you to read. NYU is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites and does not make any representations about them.

Back to Top ^

### Changes to this Privacy Statement  

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Statement in whole or in part at any time. The modified policy will be posted on this page with an updated effective date.

Back to Top ^

### Questions  

If you have questions about this Privacy Statement or the privacy practices of NYU websites or digital properties, please contact **[digital-privacy-group@nyu.edu](mailto:digital-privacy-group@nyu.edu)**.  

Effective Date: Dec 9, 2013

Back to Top ^

### University Bulletins  

New York University Bulletins are available in both electronic and printed versions. The University makes every effort to keep both current.

However, should there be a substantive difference between versions of the bulletin for a particular school, the printed bulletin is the official document. If you require further clarification, please call the Office of the Dean for that school.

Back to Top ^
